While doing research and the government will probably take time, the
tractor stock does not field above ₹10
and does not become a little stable, the
spread is special, packets of that level are far away, the
government will want to see how much, on the contrary,
in that particular price, you would
not want to convert your city into any voice, right now do not
carry the big news of the moment, now
I am not big, what is going on, as it is, we
take it with us, additionally we have
gathered in the studio again, if you tell me
old man old woman, the first stop I would like to mention is
ICICI Lombard i.e.
ICC General Insurance, if we talk about this company, then
in such a bullish market, the
stock is a little okay, it is
chatting with a decline of about 2.25 percent, here it is that
you can take two to
four trading sessions of activity, Reduce thinks that
maybe the stock will show you 25 to 30 prepaid
settings because we are a bus
running in the market, so somewhere
due to the bus of the heart, they start a little and it remains
and that is why a little bit of
worst position is written here, open interest is
around eight  It has increased by 7.5% and you can see the
market plants
in the futures market. Apart from this, you should keep an eye on HPCL
where dealers were indicating that
dominating mutual funds are under pressure. Again,
oil marketing companies are in love and
District Today we have discussed this book
but the police feel that
targets up to 270-280 can be set. That is, crude
oil, that is, crude oil,
people have been on this for about six months and perhaps from here, oil
marketing companies can show problems. Today,
after a long time, due to which
open interest of 7-8% has been seen increasing in HPCL stock
towards long and it is certain
that again today the limelight is
going towards oil marketing companies like BTC.
Whereas, Money and in the last few seconds,
if you look at the data, it is clear that the first white
route, its replacement, is up to
9578 abroad between HPCL and
BPCL, bad edit, last improvised,
behind, ginger orgy platform is here.
1201 objective was to approve the board of the bank.
This decision was taken in a meeting.
About 170 ugly if  You can see this
back here, the lock platform will be
on your skin, but it is not wild. Remember one thing,
we did two videos on this method,
but I will stop
and forget the video call in a while. I will show you
some data of Vicky Contact from September 15th.
I had fixed a target in today's morning commentary,
from which
we got approximately
1787 today. If it comes here, then
I will have a target for it during the day,
okay, it was 40,270 and Nifty Bank's
Nifty Bank drop back today is
40,266. So more or less, today on the
day of expiry, we got a huge loan on the Nifty hybrid,
John of Scientific Option Lighter, and
Nifty Bank's weekly contract,
above a call center, which
means we ran away from there, so about
three hundred and seventy five more were lost. In a while, I will
see what the next Vicky Contact data
is, but right now we also get loose BTC calls,
then I will write that data and
after that a lot of chewy  I will write that it is only
with him, let's start the BTS reaction to,
but Sachin, tell me what would you like to carry
tomorrow, a person makes a Sachin for your benefit, is it
not so, Ashish
Chaturmohata ji, keep your pick that
I will suck one of my three strokes,
I should pay attention to the Adani postpaid bill,
Tasty because the
decision line is good, the
buildup is quite strong, it is straight at the support level of 85,
top 30 should be placed,
925 love, its Lakshmi as Tasty,
I think Adani can be seen from the port.